

[Muhammad Ridwan Diansyah]

Bandung, West Java, 40266 | +62 888 1376 610 | ridwandiansyah3@gmail.com mridwandiansyah.github.io

About Me

I am Muhammad Ridwan Diansyah, currently a student at the LPKIA Digital Economics Institute majoring in Information Systems. Having internship experience as a Programmer at the Cicaheum Village Office in Bandung by creating a population data processing website using the PHP programming language and the current activity is as a lecturer assistant.

I have a career interest as Back-end Devoloper, Font-end Devoloper, System Analyzt and proficient in using Java, Python, PHP, Javascript and Node JS programming languages.

Ability & Competence

- Microsoft Office
- UI/UX Design
- Network Technician

- Database Oracle / SQL Server
- PHP & Javascript Programming
- Enterprise Resources Planning

Work Experience

Diskominfo (Bandung, Indonesia)

Network Technician (August 2018 – November 2018)

- Responsible for checking CCTV in the Bandung City area.
- Assist in checking fiber optic cables, crimping Unshielded Twisted Pair cables and inputting tower provider data.

Institute of Digital Economy LPKIA (Bandung, Indonesia)

Assistant Lecturer (October 2020 – June 2022)

- Helping the lecturers' work in teaching the material presented and helping junior level students if you have difficulties in programming languages that you can't understand.
- Job achievement: Improving communication between lecturers and students so that students understand what material is being discussed by the lecturer.

Cicaheum Village Office (Bandung , Indonesia)

Programmer (August 2021 – September 2021)

- Help record population data and make a letter to the service department.
- Job achievement: Improving the efficiency of population data management by creating a population data processing website using the PHP programming language.

Education

Institute of Digital Economy LPKIA (2019 - Present)

S1 Information Systems - Temporary GPA 3,45

- Participate in web learning workshops using wordpress and about 3D printing.
- Make scientific journal articles about the management of website-based laundry services.

Vocational High School Medikacom Bandung (2016 - 2019)

Major Computer network Engineering

• Organize competitions debian server linux configuration settings with a later one batch.

Award

- Successful completion of the Cisco international Certification exam.
- Successfully complete the Mikrotik International Certification exam.
- UI/UX Design Fundamental graduation certificate.